unbeatable.co.uk 2013-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Low Price At Unbeatable.co.uk

### Need to know:

  * We are committed to protecting your privacy and security.
  * To update your email preferences at any time, choose ‘MY ACCOUNT’ in the top menu bar and choose the ‘PREFERENCES’ tab.

### More information:

1.    Liquid New Media Limited  is responsible for the www.unbeatable.co.uk website (the "Website") and is committed to protecting your privacy and security.

2.    From time to time we may invite you to supply personal information in order for us to authenticate your identity or to provide you with services. In order to deliver such services, we will need to process and store your personal information and may need to transfer it to the relevant partner(s), to Unbeatable.co.uk’s for processing both inside and outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). By submitting your personal information, you consent to such processing and transfers in connection with such orders, offers or services and for any other purposes to which you consent at the time you provide the information or as provided in this privacy policy.

3.    Liquid New Media Limited is registered in accordance with and seeks to comply with the UK Data Protection Act 1998. We follow appropriate security procedures in the storage and disclosure of personal information so as to prevent unauthorised access by third parties. We also require those parties to whom we transfer personal information to comply with the same. However, the Internet is not a totally secure medium and you acknowledge and agree that Liquid New Media Limited shall not be responsible for any unauthorised use, distribution, damage or destruction of personal data, except to the extent We are required to accept such responsibility by the Data Protection Act 1998

4.    This Policy only applies to the use that we make of data provided to us via the Internet and email. Other uses may be made of data provided to Liquid New Media Limited in correspondence, by telephone or by other means not detailed in this Policy. These terms apply in addition to Terms & Conditions for the Website.

### 5.   Why we need to collect information from you?

We will notify you as to the types of information we are collecting about you as well as the uses we intend to make of that information. We may use the information we collect about you to notify you from time to time about important new features and changes to our online services or special offers, competitions or promotions we think you'll find of interest.

### 6.   Special promotions

Occasionally a third party may sponsor a promotion, offer, competition or page of the website and you may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. In those circumstances we may transfer personal information to those named third parties that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy policy will apply.

### 7.   Who Else Will We Provide Your Data To?

Subject to what we say below, we will not pass on your personal details to any third party, including site sponsors or advertisers, without your consent. In order to provide goods and services to you we may need to provide your data to our agents and service providers. We may provide aggregate statistics about our users, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to our third-party partners (if any), but these statistics will not contain any information about you from which you could be identified. Unbeatable.co.uk will at all times control your personal information and will remain responsible for your personal information.

If you enter any competitions on this website it may be necessary for us to provide your personal information to the promoters of the competition or to others that are involved in the organisation of the competition or the prize-giving.

Also, we may transfer your personal information to purchasers or subsidiaries (and potential purchasers or subsidiaries) if Liquid New Media Limited acquires, or is acquired by or merged with, another company. This will enable you, for example, to continue your relationship with Liquid New Media Limited despite a change of ownership.

We may also need to provide your data to our subscription and other fulfilment agents in order to provide goods or services to you (including passing on your data to our delivery partners for the purposes of arranging delivery of your products to you¬).

### 8.   Content Posted by You

Of course, if you post any personal information to any bulletin boards or forums, this information will immediately be made available to other users throughout the world who may use it to send you unsolicited communications. Furthermore, in some circumstances we may display some of your personal information (name data) when you post material to the website to allow users to identify each other.

#### The Blog

The blog is written and edited by the Unbeatable.co.uk editorial team. Unbeatable.co.uk members can now interact with the blog content and post comments in response to posted articles. Please remember that these are public spaces, so use common sense when posting with regards to sharing any personal information and writing appropriate content. Unbeatable.co.uk will retain the right to edit or remove a user comment should we deem it to be untrue, defamatory, offensive or obscene. Unbeatable.co.uk retain the right to block or ban members from posting on the blog if they continue to break the rules

### 9.   Security and possibility of international transfer.

Please note that countries outside the EEA may not have the same level of protection as countries within the EEA, but we always demand that those parties to whom we transfer data adhere to the same security procedures that we follow ourselves. By submitting your personal information, you consent to such processing and transfers in connection with such orders, offers or services and for any other purposes to which you consent at the time you provide the information.

### 10.       The Use Of 'Cookies'

In order to enable us to provide you with a personalised browsing experience, this site uses 'cookie' information collection technology. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are issued to your computer when you enter a website. Cookies are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive, and they can be used for a wide range of purposes, such as identifying your computer's previous visits to this website, and to ascertain the most popular features of this website.

### 11.       Why We Use Cookies

Like many other websites, this website uses cookies as they enable us to identify your computer when you visit this website. For example, cookies can make it possible for us to identify and automatically log in registered users of certain services on this website without the need for us to ask users for their registration details and password each time they visit. We also use cookies to develop a clearer picture of which parts of this website are the most popular to its visitors, and your preferences. You are not obliged to accept cookies and you may amend your browser's settings to prevent it from accepting cookies. The Internet Advertising Bureau provides more information on how to manage cookies on your computer. Please be aware that if you do disable cookies, certain services on this website may not be available to you and your enjoyment of this website may be impaired.

### 12.       Links and Third Party Advertising

Any links on the website may take you to third party sites over which we have no control. Similarly, advertisements appearing on this website may be posted by third parties who may use their own cookies and have their own privacy policies. When linking to another website you should read the privacy policy stated on that website. This privacy policy covers the use made of cookies and personal data by Liquid New Media Limited and does not cover the use made of cookies and personal data by any third parties.

### 13.       Feedback, Comments & Suggestions

If you have any queries about Our Privacy Policy or any queries about the protection of personal information We hold about you, please do not hesitate to contact us: Our address is:

**The Gas Super Store T/A Unbeatable.co.uk    
VAT Reg No: 316 0159 90  
68 - 72 Hinckley Road, Leicester  
LE3 0RD**

**If you have any objections to this Privacy Policy you should not submit your personal information on this website.**
